Division of Invertebrate Paleontology Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- Electronic Archives, Series VIII
  - Electronic Archives., 002431
    - Electronic Archives. Geologic excursions to the Rocky Mountains and beyond; field trip guidebook for the 1996 Annual Meeting, Geological Society of America, Denver, Colorado, Oct. 28-31, 002402
    - Electronic Archives. One compact disc (CD) containing digital photos of some of Twenhofel's type brachiopods from Anticosti Island, Canada. See reprint # 5336. Prepared in Corel Print with multiple images. electronic document; ex Argus ID=IP.D.0750.0002, 2001; 002368
    - Electronic Archives. One compact disc (CD) (Kodak Portfolio II) containing 7 digital photos of K.M. Waage; biographical; taken between 1941 and 1985; without captions. original slides belong to Elizabeth Waage and to Leo J. Hickey; electronic document; ex Argus ID=IP.D.0750.0003.; The first image is a classroom scene from Princeton University ca. 1935 showing Waage on the left (standing) and Benny Howell on the right (pointing). The second image shows a group of students, Waage is holding the dog., 2001; 002369
    - Electronic Archives. One compact disc (CD) (Kodak TIF) containing 7 digital photos of K.M. Waage; biographical; taken between 1941 and 1985; with captions; #4 is basis for Zallinger portrait. original slides belong to Elizabeth Waage and to Leo J. Hickey (#4); electronic document; ex Argus ID=IP.D.0750.0004, 2001; 002370
    - Electronic Archives. One compact disc (CD) and one Zip disc containing digital photos of Ordovician Gastropoda from Newfoundland, Canada, and specimen labels, and updates of locality and stratigraphic info.(see Rohr letter of Oct. 15, 2001). YPM.03450; 03100; electronic document; ex Argus ID=IP.D.0750.0006, 002372
    - Electronic Archives. Stromatoporoid Report, UNC Dept. of Geological Science. YPM.10753; YPM.10755; YPM.10758. ex Argus ID=IP.D.0750.0011, 2003; 002377
    - Electronic Archives. One compact disc (CD) containing digital photos of about 50 lots from systematic and type trilobites; taken by T. Whiteley. electronic document; ex Argus ID=IP.D.0750.0014, 2003; 002380
    - Electronic Archives. Thecideide (Brachiopoda) electronic images (re loans 551, 621). electronic document; ex Argus ID=IP.D.0750.0007, 2004; 002373
    - Electronic Archives. Fossils of the Burgess Shale - Digital Image Gallery/Library Electronic database - Disk A. ex Argus ID=IP.D.0750.0008, 2004; 002374
    - Electronic Archives. Fossils of the Burgess Shale - Digital Image Gallery/Library Electronic database - Disk B. ex Argus ID=IP.D.0750.0009, 2004; 002375
    - Electronic Archives. Fossils of the Burgess Shale - Digital Image Gallery/Library Electronic database - Disk C. ex Argus ID=IP.D.0750.0010, 2004; 002376
    - Electronic Archives. Stegerhynchus peneborealis, photos of two syntypes (Twenhofel, 1928). ex Argus ID=IP.D.0750.0012, 2004; 002378
    - Electronic Archives. CD with brachiopod images for monograph (publication venue undecided) including YPM 10411, YPM 10419, YPM 11129, YPM 10356, and 10413. ex Argus ID=IP.D.0750.0013, 2004; 002379
    - Electronic Archives. Brachiopods and paleoecological studies in the Pennsylvanian of the Great Basin (U. S. A.). University of Oregon, Eugene, Oregon., 2004; 002383
    - Electronic Archives. Digital images of Carpenter type specimens, which were sent to Dr. D. E. Shcherbekov, Paleontological Institute, Moscow, Russia for his use. A rights and reproduction form was sent along with a copy of this cd (February 2005). ex Argus ID=IP.D.0750.0016, 002382
    - Electronic Archives. Bing Shen - Images from April 3 to April 6, 2005 visit - Disk 1 - Ediacara Fossils - specimen list enclosed, 002384
    - Electronic Archives. Bing Shen - Images from April 3 to April 6, 2005 visit - Disk 2 - Ediacaran Fossils - specimen list enclosed, 002385
    - Electronic Archives. Bing Shen - Images from April 3 to April 6, 2005 visit - Disk 3 - Ediacaran Fossils - specimen list enclosed, 002386
    - Electronic Archives. Bing Shen - Images from April 3 to April 6, 2005 visit - Disk 4 - Ediacaran Fossils - specimen list enclosed, 002387
    - Electronic Archives. Bing Shen - Images from April 3 to April 6, 2005 visit - Disk 5 - Ediacara Fossils - specimen list enclosed, 002388
    - Electronic Archives. Images from March 31 - April 8, 2005 visit - Disk 1 - specimen list enclosed, 002389
    - Electronic Archives. Images from March 31 - April 8, 2005 visit - Disk 1 - specimen list enclosed, 002390
    - Electronic Archives. CD of Ridgemount Quarry South, Niagara Peninsula, Ontario, Canada (January 20, 2006). Photographs with captions. All photographs are of the Williamsville Waterlime (except photo of "Topographic Waterlime" from the Ellicott Creek Breccia, Fiddlers Green Formation). Photos by Samuel J. Ciurca, Jan. 20, 2006., 002391
    - Electronic Archives. Paleoecology and paleobiogeography of the New York Appalachian Basin eurypterids: Yale senior thesis. 49pp., 2009; 002412
    - Electronic Archives. 2 compact discs containing SEM photos of Onychaster vertebrae, 2010; 002415
    - Electronic Archives. Farrell, Una. 2011. Taphonomy and Paleoecology of Pyritized Trilobite Faunas from Upstate New York., 002409
    - Electronic Archives. One compact disc (CD) containing CT scans performed February 3, 2012 at Quinnipiac University., 002410
    - Electronic Archives. Six compact discs (CD) containing CT scans performed February 17, 2012 at Quinnipiac University., 002411
    - Electronic Archives. Two compact discs (CD) containing CT scans performed August 3, 2012 at Quinnipiac University., 002413
    - Electronic Archives. One compact disc (CD) containing CT scans performed May 4, 2012 at Quinnipiac University. Scans of the following specimens: USNM 439582, YPM IP 517387, YPM IP 517395, YPM IP 517397, YPM IP 516426., 002737
    - Electronic Archives. One compact disc (CD) containing the Field Guide to the Geology of the Central Lowlands in Connecticut. Prepared in Pagemaker 6.5 with multiple images. 11 p. electronic document; ex Argus ID=IP.D.0750.0001, 28 Oct 2000; 002367
    - Electronic Archives. Forney, Gerald & Nitecki, Matthew H. 1976. Fieldiana Geology. 30. Field Museum of Natural History, 29 Oct 1976; 002407
    - Electronic Archives. One compact disc (CD) (Kodak TIF) containing digital photos of Joe St. Jean's stromatoporoid collections in attic of Mitchell Hall (Geology Building), University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill (contact, Joe Carter); details of cases and drawers taken June June 9, 2001. YPM.10753; YPM.10755; YPM.10758. electronic document; ex Argus ID=IP.D.0750.0005, 002371
    - Electronic Archives. Steiner, Gerhard & Kabat, Alan R. 2004. Catalog of species-group names of Recent and fossil Scaphopoda (Mollusca). Zoosystema. 26: 549-726. ex Argus ID=IP.D.0750.0015, 002381
    - Electronic Archives. CD of photographs, Williamsville Waterlime (Bertie Group), Rochester Quarry South, Fort Erie, Niagara Peninsula, Ontario, Canada, collecting on January 13, 2006. Photographs with captions. Photos by Samuel J. Ciurca, Jan. 13, 2006., 002392
    - Electronic Archives. CD of photographs, Mistaken Point, Newfoundland. Photographs of Mistaken Point fauna, taken by Steve Pavelsky, August 4, 2004. Sent from Pavelsky to S. J. Ciurca. Ciurca sent to YPM Jan. 27, 2006., 002393
    - Electronic Archives. Ridgemount Quarry South, Ontario, Canada, March 31, 2006; Cayuga Senca Canal, Seneca Falls, N.Y., April 2, 2006: a photographic record by Samuel J. Ciurca, Jr., Rochester, New York, 002394
    - Electronic Archives. Photo CD for April 2006, Samuel J. Ciurca, Jr. Rochester, NY, CIURCA 516 Manchester-Sortsville; CIURCA 520 Gasport Quarry Medusaegraptus Beds; Gananda; Cayuga-Seneca Canal; CIURCA 523 Seneca Falls Sewage Treatment; CIURCA 522 (NEW) Akron Dolostone; CIURCA 13 Neid Road Quarrry; etc., 002395
    - Electronic Archives. Late Silurian Bertie Group, Mud Creek, East of Victor, New York, November 18, 2005 (Ciurca NY Loc. 20): 'a photographic record by Samuel J. Ciurca, Jr.', 002396
    - Electronic Archives. Tiny Eurypterid Specimen; research specimen info sent to Sam Ciurca, Jr.; photos of a specimen (probably Eurypterus remipes) from the Ellicott Creek Breccia, Fiddlers Green Fm., Bertie Group. Ridgemount Q South, Fort Erie, Ontario, Canada. Collected by Peter Lee of Ontario, Canada during the Summer of 2005. CD and letters ondated to the Yale Pabody Museum, New Haven, CT during Aug. 2005., 002397
    - Electronic Archives. Miscellaneous sites compiled June 3, 2006, Sam Ciurca, Jr.,. Quarry in the Forge Hollow Gypsum, Owasco Outlet, Pterygotid/Stromatolite Bed. Ridgemount Quarry South Excavating Williamsville Waterlime. Ellicott Creek Breccia, in Eastern RQS. More Ridgemount Quarry South.. Olney Fm., etc., 002398
    - Electronic Archives. Off to the Yale Peabody Museum: the Ciurca Eurypterid Collection: 'a photographic record of the great move, photos taken June 3-6, 2005 by Samuel J. Ciurca, Rochester, NY, 002399
    - Electronic Archives. Ridgemount Quarry South November 11, 2005 (includes Dolichopterus): a photographic record of one day in the life of eurypterid collectors at Fort Erie, Niagara Peninsula, Ontario, Canada, Williamsville Waterlime (Bertie Group) only. Photos taken by Samuel J. Ciurca, Jr. Nov. 11, 2005, 002400
    - Electronic Archives. New York State Geological Association. 77th Annual Meeting, Oswego, New York: 'a photographic record of "Fractures & Faults in the Eastern Lake Ontario Basin, Oswego County (A-3) and part of "Eurypterids & Facies changes within Silurian/Devonian 'Eurypterus Beds' of New York State" (B-4). Photos taken by Sam Ciurca, Sept. 24 & 25, 2005, 002401
    - Electronic Archives. Antero Formation bugs - taken during visit July 21-27, 2008, Schuchert and Dubar Grants in Aid visitor, 002403
    - Electronic Archives. Brachiopods - photographed on Aug 22, 2008, 002404
    - Electronic Archives. Burgess Shale fossils from R.O.M. - actual specimens that were modeled, 002405
    - Electronic Archives. Photographs - Ceratiocarids (mostly), May 27-30, 2008 visit, 002406
    - Electronic Archives. Meek, Fielding B. & Worthen, Amos H. 1860. Descriptions of New Carboniferous Fossils from Illinois and other Western States. Proceedings of the Academy of Natural Sciences of Philadelphia. 12: 447-462., 002408
    - Electronic Archives. Field notes (images) 12 Oct 2012 - Ellicott Creek Breccia at Ridgemount Quarry South, Ontario, Canada, 002414
    - 1 external hard drive which serves as a backup (2) for TIDE 2016 from the Hull lab., 002723
- Exhibits, Series IX
  Exhibit-related material
  - Exhibit Openings. Material related to exhibit openings., 002739
    - Electronic Archives. Compact disc (CD) of photos from the opening of the West Haven Concretions exhibit, 23 Dec 2003; 002740